{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Easy",
      "category": "Numbers",
      "question": "What number is 7 in Maori?",
      "correct_answer": "Whitu",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Tahi",
        "Toru",
        "Waru"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "Easy",
      "category": "Numbers",
      "question": "What is the number 1 in Maori?",
      "correct_answer": "Tahi",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Rua",
        "Ono",
        "Whitu"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Numbers",
      "question": "What is the number 4 in Maori?",
      "correct_answer": "Wha",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Rua",
        "Ono",
        "Tahi"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Cities",
      "question": "What is the Maori name of Wellington?",
      "correct_answer": "Te Whanganui-a-Tara",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Tāmaki Makaurau",
        "Ōtautahi",
        "Awakairangi"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Cities",
      "question": "What is the Maori name of Christchurch?",
      "correct_answer": "Ōtautahi",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Te Whanganui-a-Tara",
        "Tāmaki Makaurau",
        "Awakairangi"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Cities",
      "question": "What is the Maori name of Queenstown?",
      "correct_answer": "Tāhuna",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ōtautahi",
        "Tāmaki Makaurau",
        "Awakairangi"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Months",
      "question": "What is the Maori name for October?",
      "correct_answer": "Whiringa-ā-nuku",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Hakihea",
        "Haratua",
        "Whiringa-ā-rangi "
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Months",
      "question": "What is the Maori name for December?",
      "correct_answer": "Hakihea",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Whiringa-ā-nuku",
        "Haratua",
        "Whiringa-ā-rangi"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Months",
      "question": "What is the Maori name for February?",
      "correct_answer": "Hui-tanguru",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Hakihea",
        "Haratua",
        "Whiringa-ā-rangi"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Months",
      "question": "What is the Maori name for June?",
      "correct_answer": "Pipiri",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Hakihea",
        "Haratua",
        "Whiringa-ā-rangi"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
